writersstore.com 2011-03-18

# Privacy Policy for writersstore.com

Effective on October 19, 2010

This privacy statement describes how The Writers Store, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [writersstore.com](http://writersstore.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

**TRUSTe**

The Writers Store, Inc. is a Participant in the TRUSTe Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to advance privacy and trust in the networked world. This Web site has agreed to have its privacy practices monitored for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at [customer-service@writersstore.com](mailto:customer-service@writersstore.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Respond to your questions and concerns

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [customer-service@writersstore.com](mailto:customer-service@writersstore.com).

We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.

**Information Obtained from Third Parties**

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if The Writers Store, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

_PayPal_

If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

_Amazon_

If you choose to use Amazon to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to Amazon. Amazon's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on Amazon's Web site

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

_Web beacons_

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

_Links to Other Web Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of The Writers Store, Inc.. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [customer-service@writersstore.com](mailto:customer-service@writersstore.com)

We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third party payment option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose to use a third party payment option to pay for your order, its privacy statement and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

## Additional Policy Information

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [customer-service@writersstore.com](mailto:customer-service@writersstore.com).

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

The Writers Store, Inc.

3510 West Magnolia Blvd. 

Burbank, CA, United States 91505

Phone: 800 272-8927
